<resources>
    <string name="app_name">InfoApp</string>
    <string name="salah">Mohamed Salah Hamed Mahrous Ghaly (Arabic: محمد صلاح حامد محروس غالي, Egyptian Arabic pronunciation: [mæˈħam.mæd sˤɑˈlɑːħ ˈɣæːli];[5] born 15 June 1992), known as Mohamed Salah or Mo Salah, is an Egyptian professional footballer who plays as a right winger or forward for Premier League club Liverpool and captains the Egypt national team. Regarded as one of the best players of his generation and among the greatest African players of all time, he is known for his clinical finishing, dribbling and speed.[6][7][8]\n\nSalah started his senior career in 2010 playing for Al Mokawloon Al Arab, departing in 2012 to join Basel, where he won two Swiss Super League titles. In 2014, Salah joined Chelsea for a reported fee of £11 million, but limited gametime led to successive loans to Fiorentina and Roma, who later signed him permanently for €15 million. In the 2016–17 season, Salah was a key figure in Roma\'s unsuccessful title bid, reaching double figures in both goals and assists. In 2017, Salah was transferred to Liverpool for £36.9 million, a club record at the time. In his first season, he set the record for most Premier League goals scored (32) in a 38-game season and helped Liverpool to the 2018 UEFA Champions League final. Having formed a formidable attacking trio with Roberto Firmino and Sadio Mané after the departure of Philippe Coutinho, Salah went on to be an integral player in the club\'s Champions League and Premier League title successes in the following two seasons, and has since also won the FA Cup, EFL Cup and FA Community Shield. Salah has achieved numerous individual accolades, including two PFA Players\' Player of the Year awards, three Premier League Golden Boots, the Premier League Player of the Season, the Premier League Playmaker of the Season, finished third for the Best FIFA Men\'s Player in 2018 and 2021, and finished fifth in the 2019 and 2022 FIFA Ballon d\'Or. He received the 2018 FIFA Puskás Award for his winning strike in the first Merseyside derby of the 2017–18 season. In 2023, Salah became Liverpool\'s top Premier League goalscorer, and became the fifth player to score 200 goals for the club.</string>
    <string name="lewan">Robert Lewandowski (Polish pronunciation: [ˈrɔbɛrt lɛvanˈdɔfskʲi] ⓘ; born 21 August 1988) is a Polish professional footballer who plays as a striker for La Liga club Barcelona and captains the Poland national team. He is regarded as one of the best players of his generation and as one of the best strikers of all time, as well as the most successful player in Bundesliga and Bayern Munich history. He has scored over 600 senior career goals for club and country.\n\nAfter being the top scorer in the third and second tiers of Polish football with Znicz Pruszków, Lewandowski moved to top-flight Lech Poznań, helping the team win the 2009–10 Ekstraklasa. In 2010, he transferred to Borussia Dortmund, where he won honors including two consecutive Bundesliga titles and the league\'s top goalscorer award. In 2013, he also featured with Dortmund in the 2013 UEFA Champions League final. Prior to the start of the 2014–15 season, Lewandowski agreed to join Dortmund\'s domestic rivals, Bayern Munich, on a free transfer. In Munich, he won the Bundesliga title in every one of his eight seasons. Lewandowski was integral in Bayern\'s UEFA Champions League win in 2019–20 as part of a treble. He is one of only two players, alongside Johan Cruyff, to achieve the European treble while being the highest goalscorer in all three competitions, and the first to do it as the sole top scorer.[4][5] Lewandowski is also one of only two players to be top goalscorer for club and country in Europe for three consecutive years (2019–21), alongside Cristiano Ronaldo.[6][7] He was widely considered the best player of 2020 and deserving of the Ballon d\'Or, until it was canceled.[8][9][10][11] In 2022, he was signed by Barcelona, where he won the Supercopa de España, the La Liga title and the Pichichi Trophy in his debut season. He holds the joint-record for most top scorer awards in Europe\'s top five leagues with eight, alongside Lionel Messi, and the joint-record for the most consecutive with six, alongside Kylian Mbappé.</string>
    <string name="ronaldo">Cristiano Ronaldo dos Santos Aveiro GOIH ComM (Portuguese pronunciation: [kɾiʃˈtjɐnu ʁɔˈnaldu]; born 5 February 1985) is a Portuguese professional footballer who plays as a forward for and captains both Saudi Pro League club Al Nassr and the Portugal national team. Widely regarded as one of the greatest players of all time, Ronaldo has won five Ballon d\'Or awards,[note 3] a record three UEFA Men\'s Player of the Year Awards, and four European Golden Shoes, the most by a European player. He has won 33 trophies in his career, including seven league titles, five UEFA Champions Leagues, the UEFA European Championship and the UEFA Nations League. Ronaldo holds the records for most appearances (183), goals (140) and assists (42) in the Champions League, goals in the European Championship (14), international goals (128) and international appearances (206). He is one of the few players to have made over 1,200 professional career appearances, the most by an outfield player, and has scored over 890 official senior career goals for club and country, making him the top goalscorer of all time.\n\nRonaldo began his senior career with Sporting CP, before signing with Manchester United in 2003, winning the FA Cup in his first season. He would also go on to win three consecutive Premier League titles, the Champions League and the FIFA Club World Cup; at age 23, he won his first Ballon d\'Or. Ronaldo was the subject of the then-most expensive association football transfer when he signed for Real Madrid in 2009 in a transfer worth €94 million (£80 million). He became a key contributor and formed an attacking trio with Karim Benzema and Gareth Bale which was integral to the team winning four Champions Leagues from 2014 to 2018, including La Décima. During this period, he won back-to-back Ballons d\'Or in 2013 and 2014, and again in 2016 and 2017, and was runner-up three times behind Lionel Messi, his perceived career rival. He also became the club\'s all-time top goalscorer and the all-time top scorer in the Champions League, and finished as the competition\'s top scorer for six consecutive seasons between 2012 and 2018. With Real, Ronaldo won four Champions Leagues, two La Liga titles, two Copas del Rey, two UEFA Super Cups and three Club World Cups. In 2018, he signed for Juventus in a transfer worth an initial €100 million (£88 million), the most expensive transfer for an Italian club and for a player over 30 years old. He won two Serie A titles, two Supercoppa Italiana trophies and a Coppa Italia, became the inaugural Serie A Most Valuable Player and became the first footballer to finish as top scorer in the English, Spanish and Italian leagues. He returned to Manchester United in 2021, finishing his only full season as the club\'s top scorer, before his contract was terminated in 2022. In 2023, he signed for Al Nassr.</string>
    <string name="messi">Lionel Andrés \"Leo\" Messi[note 1] (Spanish pronunciation: [ljoˈnel anˈdɾes ˈmesi] ⓘ; born 24 June 1987) is an Argentine professional footballer who plays as a forward for and captains both Major League Soccer club Inter Miami and the Argentina national team. Widely regarded as one of the greatest players of all time, Messi has won a record eight Ballon d\'Or awards, a record six European Golden Shoes, and was named the world\'s best player for a record eight times by FIFA.[note 2] Until 2021, he had spent his entire professional career with Barcelona, where he won a club-record 34 trophies, including ten La Liga titles, seven Copa del Rey titles, and the UEFA Champions League four times. With his country, he won the 2021 Copa América and the 2022 FIFA World Cup. A prolific goalscorer and creative playmaker, Messi holds the records for most goals (474), hat-tricks (36), and assists in La Liga (192). He has the most international goals by a South American male (106). Messi has scored over 800 senior career goals for club and country, and the most goals for a single club (672).\n\nMessi relocated to Spain and joined Barcelona aged 13, making his competitive debut at age 17 in October 2004. He established himself as an integral player for the club within the next three years, and in his first uninterrupted season in 2008–09 helped Barcelona achieve the first treble in Spanish football; that year, aged 22, Messi won his first Ballon d\'Or. Messi won four consecutive Ballons d\'Or, the first player to win it four times. During the 2011–12 season, he set La Liga and European records for most goals in a season, while establishing himself as Barcelona\'s all-time top scorer. The following two seasons, he finished second for the Ballon d\'Or behind Cristiano Ronaldo, his perceived career rival, before regaining his best form during the 2014–15 campaign, becoming the all-time top scorer in La Liga and leading Barcelona to a historic second treble, and was awarded a fifth Ballon d\'Or in 2015. Messi assumed captaincy of Barcelona in 2018, and won a record sixth Ballon d\'Or in 2019. He signed for French club Paris Saint-Germain in August 2021, spending two seasons there and winning Ligue 1 twice. Messi joined American club Inter Miami in July 2023, winning the Leagues Cup in August.\n</string>
    <string name="haaland">Erling Braut Haaland (né Håland; Urban East Norwegian: [ˈhòːlɑn];[5] born 21 July 2000) is a Norwegian professional footballer who plays as a striker for Premier League club Manchester City and the Norway national team. Considered one of the best players in the world, he is known for his speed, strength, positioning, and finishing inside the box. In his debut Premier League season, Haaland broke the record for the most goals scored by a player in a single season, with 36.[6]\n\nComing through the youth system, Haaland played for Norwegian sides Bryne and Molde, before relocating to Austria with Red Bull Salzburg in January 2019. His performances there earned him a move to Bundesliga club Borussia Dortmund, where he won the DFB-Pokal in 2021. In the summer of 2022, he transferred to Manchester City for a fee of €60 million (£51.2 million), and was instrumental in the club winning a continental treble in his debut campaign; his 52 goals across all competitions was the most ever for a Premier League player. Haaland was named the league\'s Young Player and Player of the Season, becoming the first player to win both awards in the same year.\n\nHaaland has won several individual awards and broken various records during his career, including the 2020 Golden Boy award, while in 2021 he was named Bundesliga Player of the Season, in addition to his inclusion in the FIFA FIFPro World11 for 2021, 2022 and 2023. He has also broken multiple Premier League records, including most goals scored in a season, the quickest individual to score two, three, four and five hat-tricks, and the first in league history to score hat-tricks in three consecutive home games. In 2023, he won the Premier League Golden Boot, the European Golden Shoe and the Gerd Müller Trophy for his goalscoring success. In the same year, his performances led him to be named UEFA Men\'s Player of the Year, IFFHS World\'s Best Player and finish runner-up in the Ballon d\'Or.</string>
    <string name="kylian">Kylian Mbappé Lottin (born 20 December 1998) is a French professional footballer who played as a forward for Ligue 1 club Paris Saint-Germain and captains the France national team. Widely regarded as one of the best players in the world, he is known for his dribbling, speed, and finishing.[2][3][4] He will join La Liga club Real Madrid on 1 July 2024.\n\nBorn in Paris and raised in nearby Bondy, Mbappé began his senior club career in 2015 with Monaco, where he won the Ligue 1 title in the 2016–17 season. In 2017, aged 18, Mbappé signed for Paris Saint-Germain on an eventual permanent transfer worth €180 million, making him the second-most-expensive player and most expensive teenage player of all time.[5] With PSG, he won six Ligue 1 titles and four Coupes de France, including a domestic quadruple in the 2019–20 season, while also leading the club to its first ever UEFA Champions League final in 2020. He is the club\'s all-time top goalscorer and ranks third in assists, as was the seventh-highest goalscorer in Ligue 1 history.\n\nAt international level, Mbappé made his senior debut for France in 2017, at age of 18. At the 2018 FIFA World Cup, Mbappé became the youngest French player to score at a World Cup, as well as the second teenager, after Pelé, to score in a World Cup final. He finished as the joint second-highest goalscorer as France won the tournament; he went on to win the FIFA World Cup Best Young Player and French Player of the Year awards for his performances. He also helped France to victory in the UEFA Nations League in 2021, receiving the top scorer award in the finals. At the 2022 FIFA World Cup, France reached the final again; Mbappé won the Golden Boot and Silver Ball and set the record for the most goals scored in World Cup final matches by scoring a hat-trick. Mbappé is one of only two players to have scored in two consecutive World Cup finals (the other being Brazil\'s Vavá in 1958 and 1962).</string>
    <string name="neymar">Neymar da Silva Santos Júnior (born 5 February 1992), also known as Neymar Júnior, is a Brazilian professional footballer who plays as a attacking midfielder for Saudi Pro League club Al Hilal and the Brazil national team. Regarded as one of the greatest players in his generation, he is renowned for his flamboyant style of play, passing abilities, and two-footedness.[3][4][5][6][7][8] Neymar has scored at least 100 goals for three different clubs, being one of a few players to do so,[9] and is the highest-scoring Brazilian player in Champions League history.[10] Neymar is also the top goalscorer of all time for Brazil\'s National Football Team in official games.[11]\n\nNeymar made his professional debut with Santos in 2009, and in 2011, he helped them win their first Copa Libertadores in nearly 50 years.[12] In 2013, he joined Barcelona and became part of an attacking trio with Lionel Messi and Luis Suárez, dubbed MSN. Winning the continental treble of La Liga, the Copa del Rey, and the UEFA Champions League in the trio\'s first season, Neymar was the joint-top scorer of the Champions League campaign and top scorer in the Copa del Rey. Neymar joined Paris Saint-Germain (PSG) in 2017 in a transfer costing €222 million, making him the most expensive player ever.[note 1][15] There, he won Ligue 1 Player of the Year, won five Ligue 1 titles, and was integral to PSG being runners-up in the 2019-20 Champions League. He also ranks as PSG\'s fourth-highest all-time top goalscorer, despite reoccurring injuries consistently disrupting his playing time. In 2023, he became the most expensive signing in Saudi Pro League history, costing €90 million, as he signed for Al Hilal.\n\nDebuting for Brazil aged 18, Neymar is the nation\'s all-time top goalscorer, with 79 goals in 128 matches. He won the 2013 FIFA Confederations Cup, winning the Golden Ball. In the 2014 FIFA World Cup, he was named in the Dream Team. He captained Brazil to their first Olympic gold medal in men\'s football at the 2016 Summer Olympics, having already achieving a silver medal at the 2012 edition. Helping Brazil to a runner-up finish at the 2021 Copa América, he was jointly awarded Best Player. In the 2022 World Cup, he became the third Brazilian player to score in three World Cups, after Pelé and Ronaldo. Neymar has won a record six Samba Gold awards.</string>
    <string name="shoma">Eldor Azamat oʻgʻli Shomurodov (born 29 June 1995) is an Uzbek professional footballer who plays as a forward for Serie A club Cagliari, on loan from Roma. He also captains the Uzbekistan national team.\n\nShomurodov played in his homeland for Mash\'al Mubarek and Bunyodkor before spending three years with Rostov in the Russian Premier League. In 2020, he moved to Genoa in Serie A for €8 million and a year later Roma for €17.5 million. After helping the under-20 team to the quarter-finals of the 2015 FIFA U-20 World Cup, he made his full international debut later that year and represented the country at the 2019 AFC Asian Cup.\n\nClub career\nEarly career\nBorn in Jarqoʻrgʻon, Shomurodov played for Mash\'al Mubarek and Bunyodkor. On 15 July 2017, he moved to Russian Premier League club Rostov. His most prolific season was his last, with 11 goals in 2019–20.[3]\n\nGenoa\nOn 1 October 2020, Shomurodov completed an €8 million move to Serie A club Genoa. He became the second Uzbek to play in Serie A, after Ilyos Zeytulayev, whose teams also included Genoa.[3] He made his debut on 19 October in a goalless draw at Hellas Verona, being substituted for Gianluca Scamacca after 63 minutes;[4] his first goal on 30 November was consolation in a 2–1 home loss to Parma.[5] He scored eight times in his one season at the Stadio Luigi Ferraris, including two in a 4–3 home loss to Atalanta on 15 May 2021.[6]\n\nRoma\nOn 2 August 2021, Roma announced the acquisition of Shomurodov on a five-year contract for €17.5 million plus bonuses.[7] He debuted 17 days later in José Mourinho\'s first game as manager, away to Trabzonspor in the first leg of the UEFA Europa Conference League playoffs. He started the game and scored the decisive goal of a 2–1 win.[8] Mainly a substitute in his first season, he scored three league goals, starting with an equaliser in a 3–2 loss at Venezia on 7 November.[9] He went on to become the first-ever Uzbek football player to win a major UEFA competition, as his club triumphed in the 2022 UEFA Europa Conference League Final, for which he was a last-minute substitute.[10]\n\nOn 30 January 2023, Spezia signed Shomurodov on loan until the end of the season.[11]\n\nOn 27 July 2023, recently-promoted to Serie A side Cagliari announced the signing of Shomurodov from Roma on a season-long loan with an option to make the move permanent.[12]</string>
    <string name="son">Son Heung-min (Korean: 손흥민; Korean pronunciation: [son.ɣɯŋ.min]; born 8 July 1992) is a South Korean professional footballer who plays as a forward for and captains both Premier League club Tottenham Hotspur and the South Korea national team.[3] Often regarded as the greatest Asian footballer of all time, he is known for his speed, finishing, two-footedness, and ability to link play.[6][7]\n\nBorn in Chuncheon, South Korea, Son relocated to Germany to join Hamburger SV at 16, making his debut in the Bundesliga in 2010. In 2013, he moved to Bayer Leverkusen for a club record €10 million before signing for Tottenham for £22 million two years later, becoming the most expensive Asian player in history.[8] While at Tottenham, Son became the top Asian goalscorer in both Premier League and Champions League history,[9] and surpassed Cha Bum-kun\'s record for most goals scored by a Korean player in European competition.[10][11][12] In 2019, he became the second Asian in history to reach and start a UEFA Champions League final after compatriot Park Ji-sung.[13] In the 2021–22 season, alongside Mohamed Salah, he won the Premier League Golden Boot award with 23 goals, becoming the first Asian player to win it.[14] In April 2023, he became the first Asian player to score 100 Premier League goals. He is also the club\'s fifth-highest goalscorer and all-time leader in assists. Son is the third Tottenham player to make 300 Premier League appearances for the club, after Hugo Lloris and Harry Kane.[15]\n\nA full international since 2010, Son has represented South Korea at the 2014, 2018, and 2022 FIFA World Cups and is his country\'s joint top scorer at World Cups, tied with Park Ji-sung and Ahn Jung-hwan on three goals. Son has also represented South Korea at the 2018 Asian Games, where the team won gold, and the 2011, 2015, 2019, and 2023 editions of the AFC Asian Cup; Korea was the runner-up in 2015.</string>
    <string name="benzema">Karim Mostafa Benzema (Arabic: كريم مصطفى بن زيما; born 19 December 1987) is a French professional footballer who plays as a striker for Saudi Pro League club Al-Ittihad. Regarded as one of the best strikers of all time, he is a creative forward known for his technical skills, vision and versatility on the field,[4][5][6] Benzema is Real Madrid\'s all-time second-highest goalscorer and top assist provider.[7] He won 25 trophies with Real Madrid, including four La Liga, three Copa del Rey, and five UEFA Champions League titles.[8] He has scored over 500 career goals for club and country.\n\nBorn in Lyon to parents of Algerian descent, Benzema began his career with hometown club Lyon in 2005, contributing sporadically to three Ligue 1 title wins. In 2008, he was named the league\'s Player of the Year and in the Team of the Year having finished as the league\'s top goalscorer and winning his fourth league title and first Coupe de France. In 2009, Benzema was the subject of a then-French record football transfer when he joined Real Madrid in a deal worth €35 million. After struggling to establish himself in his debut season, he eventually achieved a consistent goalscoring rate with the club, notably being part of a highly rated trio alongside Cristiano Ronaldo and Gareth Bale — dubbed \"BBC\" — who were integral to four Champions League wins between 2014 and 2018.\n\nFollowing Ronaldo\'s departure in 2018, Benzema transitioned from the false 9 position into a sole striker. He was named in the La Liga Team of the Season for five consecutive years from 2018 to 2023, won La Liga Best Player twice and the Pichichi Trophy for the first time in 2022. Benzema finished as Champions League top scorer as he won his fifth title in 2022, and subsequently captained the club in his final season before signing for Al-Ittihad the following year.</string>

</resources>